[music]
Woo. Okay.
>> What do we got, Karen?
>> Well, we have another snack today and
it's zucchini. It's a zucchini roll. You
know anything about zucchini?
>> Well, the problem with zucchini is so
bland. You got to spice it up. So, I
think you did that with this.
>> Yes. And this is a zucchini roll with uh
herb goat cheese and capers. And it's
lovely. And if you see on this plate
here, I made little tiny ones just for
nibbling. You can stick a little
toothpick through it, serve it, but
you'll also see larger ones. And and
what's really cool about this is you can
make them as large as you want. And
something larger like that would be a
beautiful side to some fish or
>> something like a whole meal on your
plate. So it can be a side dish or a
snacky.
>> Very flavorful.
>> Yeah, really simple. Um that's it.
>> Let's show you how to make it.
Heat. Heat. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> Okay, so to get the recipe,
>> click the link below. Hey, Charlie.
Click the link below. Below.
>> Check it out.